Guide to the William Heyen Papers YCAL MSS 352
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2023 Acquisition, 1937-2022; 12.76 Linear Feet 35 boxes
  - Writings, 1970-2022; 8.33 Linear Feet (17 boxes)
    - Writings of others
      - Townsend, Carol: Color of shadows, undated (Box 107)
      - White, Bart: 3. The art of restoration draft copy, 2021 August 18 (Box 107)
      - White, Bart: Weight of the world poems by Bart White draft #2 manuscript, 2021 August 6 (Box 107)
      - Zazulyer, Leah: As long as we are not alone, 2014 (Box 108)
      - Zazulyer, Leah: Polish-Jewish poets in the Americas, undated (Box 108)
      - Unidentified author: Crazy Horse and the Custers, William Heyen, Nine Point Publishing, undated (Box 108)
      - Unidentified author: Contents (for forthcoming Arcadia Road), 2014 (Box 108)
  - Professional papers, 1972-2017; 1.08 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
    - Annual report & review, 1989-1992 (Box 109)
    - AWP lecture, undated (Box 109)
    - Axelrod, David: curriculum vitae, undated (Box 109)
    - Bibliography, undated; 2 Folders (Box 109)
    - Catlin essay, undated (Box 109)
    - Chautauqua, 2007; 2017 (Box 109)
    - Christmas cards article, undated (Box 109)
    - Descriptive bibliography, undated (Box 109)
    - Diana, Charles & the Queen, 1997 (Box 109)
    - Distinguished prof. refs, 1999 (Box 109)
    - D. S. I., 1981-1993; 6 Folders (Box 109)
    - D. S. I., 1985-1993; 4 Folders (Box 110)
    - Etruscan Press, 2016 (Box 110)
    - Faculty master schedule, 2016 (Box 110)
    - Family tree, 1981 January 15 (Box 110)
    - Free verse and I sing myself: contract, 2016 February 4 (Box 110)
    - George Garrett, undated (Box 110)
    - Germany, undated (Box 110)
    - Grades-last 3 years, 1985-1999 (Box 110)
    - Heart, 1981 January 21 (Box 110)
    - High school, 1997; 2001 (Box 110)
    - Holocaust note, 1985 (Box 110)
    - Memorial Day Brockport, 1981 (Box 110)
    - Misc., 1988-2002 (Box 110)
    - Movie stuff, 1985-2001 (Box 110)
    - NCC talks, 1995-1997 (Box 110)
    - Open SUNY textbooks program contract, undated (Box 110)
    - Permissions, 2001-2002 (Box 110)
    - Piccione, Anthony, 1998-2001 (Box 110)
    - Poetry collection Lockwood Memorial Library SUNY AB photocopies, undated (Box 110)
    - Ribbons: the Gulf War-a poem contract, 1991 June 5 (Box 110)
    - Royalty statements, 2010-2012 (Box 110)
    - Sabbatical, 1981-1989; 3 Folders (Box 111)
    - Sake gold, 2003 (Box 111)
    - Salary, promotions, etc., 1972-1981 (Box 111)
    - Stillness moon: an interview, 2015 (Box 111)
    - V & R Books collection opening, 2000; undated (Box 111)
  - Personal papers, 1937-2020; .67 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
    - Birthday reminder book, undated (Box 112)
    - Brockport Homecoming & Family Weekend badge, undated (Box 112)
    - Calendar, 2015 (Box 112)
    - Checkbook register, 2003-2015; 3 Folders (Box 112)
    - Children's notes, undated (Box 112)
    - Datebook, 2004-2014; 9 Folders (Box 112)
    - Heyen family estate, 1991 (Box 112)
    - Lakeside Homecare Center, 2005-2007 (Box 112)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 Folders (Box 112)
    - Printed material, 1937-2016 (Box 112)
    - Programs, 1971-2015 (Box 112)
    - Student financial aid, 1968-1970 (Box 112)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous papers, 1988-2020; 7 Folders (Box 113)
      These files contain unsorted papers including notes, letters, etc.
  - Computer media, undated
    - 120'00' A conversation with John Cage by Larry A. Fader, undated; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 114)
    - Bookcase photos, undated; 1 CD-Rs (Box 114)